Guide to the Edwin H. Armstrong papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Records of Cravath, Swaine and Moore and Other Legal Firms, 1901-1982
  - Brumbaugh, Graves, Donohue and Raymond--Darby and Darby--Litigation
    - Armstrong vs. Emerson Radio and Phonograph Corp.
      - Transcript of Testimony--Pages 2018-2913, (6 Folders) (Box 235, Folder 1-6)
      - Pleadings, 1953-1956 (Box 235, Folder 7)
      - Suit Binder, 1953-1960, (2 Folders) (Box 235, Folder 8-9)
      - Correspondence, 1955-1970, (4 Folders) (Box 235, Folder 10-13)
      - Settlement Agreements and Covenant Not to Sue, 1960, 1970 (Box 235, Folder 14)
      - Settlement Negotiations, 1949-1960 (Box 235, Folder 15)
      - Annual Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 235, Folder 16)
    - Armstrong vs. Motorola, Inc.
      - Briefs, 1950 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Defendant's Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusion of Law, 1962 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Briefs, 1962-1966, undated, (4 Folders) (Box 236, Folder 3-6)
      - Transcript of Proceedings, 1963-1964 (Box 236, Folder 7)
      - Book of Exhibits, undated (Box 236, Folder 8)
      - General, 1944-1960 (Box 236, Folder 9)
      - Comparison Charts, undated (Box 236, Folder 10)
      - Brief, 1960 (Box 236, Folder 11)
      - Pre-Trial, 1960 (Box 236, Folder 12)
      - Plaintiff's Documents, 1960 (Box 236, Folder 13)
      - Diagrams From Armstrong File on Transmitter and Receiver, undated (Box 236, Folder 14)
      - Diagrams and Memoranda, 1960 (Box 236, Folder 15)
      - Notes for Oral Argument--Court of Appeals, undated (Box 236, Folder 16)
      - Brief, 1967 (Box 236, Folder 17)
      - List of Defendant's Exhibits, 1961 (Box 236, Folder 18)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits, undated (Box 236, Folder 19)
      - United States Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit--Appendix to Brief for Defendant-Appellant, 1961 (Box 236)
      - Memoranda, 1960-1961 (Box 236, Folder 20)
      - Comments for Dean Town on Motorola's Demonstration of February 16, 1961 (Box 236, Folder 21)
      - Examination of Daniel Noble, undated (Box 236, Folder 22)
      - Memoranda of Law and Fact, 1954-1956 (Box 236, Folder 23)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits, 1958, (2 Folders) (Box 236, Folder 24-25)
      - Three-Dimensional
        - Plaintiff's Exhibit No. 32-G--Vacuum Tube, 1958 October 14 (Box 251)
        - Plaintiff's Exhibit No. 32-H--Variable Capacitor, 1958 October 14 (Box 252)
        - Plaintiff's Exhibit No. 32-I--Coupled Inductor, 1958 October 14 (Box 252)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibit No. 44--Fortune Magazine, 1939 October (Box 250)
      - Magnetic Tape Recordings--5 inch and 7 inch
        - Defendant's Exhibit D-90--"Tape Recordings of the Proceedings During the Demonstrations on Behalf of Defendant at the Motorola Plant November 28-29, 1961 Including the Sound and Testimony (four large reels in Boxes Nos. 1 to 4) and the Tape Recording Actually Used in Demonstrations No. 4 (Box No. 5)"--Five Magnetic Tapes (Box 246)
        - Plaintiff's Exhibit No. 37-A--"#6--Professor Armstrong Print--Frequency Amplitude Modulation, W2AG #1"--"Label: H.E.R. Laboratories, Inc., 457 W. 46th Street, NY, June-January, May be Identical to Tape #2," 1957 October 7 (Box 246)
        - Plaintiff's Exhibit No. 37-B--"#4--Int. Carrier; FM and AM Comparisons; Interfering FM Signals; Interfering AM Signals"--"Very Good; Quality of Input Somewhat Marred by Over Drive," 1957 October 7 (Box 246)
        - Plaintiff's Exhibit No. 37-C--"#3--Professor Armstrong Print; W2AG on FM and W2XOV on AM #4"--"H.E.R. Laboratories, Inc., 457 W. 46th Street, NY, June-January, WLXOV--Static Very Bad," 1957 October 7 (Box 246)
        - Plaintiff's Exhibit No. 37-D--"Copy #1 of Haddonfield Recordings--AM-FM Static Comparison, 1935--Frank Crummet Ipana Program--Warner Quiben Glee Club," 1958 October 22 (Box 246)
        - Motorola Demonstrations--Reels Nos. 1-3, undated (Box 246)
      - Pre-Trial Briefs, 1960 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Transcript of Proceedings, 1961 February 15-16 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Plaintiff's Trial Memo, 1960 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Plaintiff's Reply Memo, 1960 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Plaintiffs' Exhibit--FCC "Aural Broadcasting on Frequencies above 25,000 K.C.," 1940 March 18 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits and Digest of Testimony, undated (Box 237, Folder 6)
      - Pleadings, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 237, Folder 7-8)
      - Petition for Certiorari, 1967 (Box 237, Folder 9)
      - Report of Court Expert George Town, 1961 March 24 (Box 237, Folder 10)
      - HS-89 and Motorola's Curve Circuit Drawing, 1961 (Box 237, Folder 11)
      - Comparison Charts, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 237, Folder 12-13)
      - Publications and Articles--Background on Short-Wave, 1915-1963, (3 Folders) (Box 237, Folder 14-16)
      - Suit for Infringement of Patents Nos. 1,941,066; 1,941,068; 1,941,069; 2,098,698; RE 21,660, 1960, (3 Folders) (Box 237, Folder 17-19)
      - Pleadings, Pre-Trial Conferences
        - Pre-Trial Memoranda, undated (Box 238, Folder 1)
        - Lists of Exhibits, Stipulations, 1960 (Box 238, Folder 2)
        - Memoranda, Notes, Conference Agendas, 1961 (Box 238, Folder 3)
        - Plaintiff's Briefs and Memoranda, undated (Box 238, Folder 4)
        - Plaintiff's Memoranda and Correspondence, 1960 (Box 238, Folder 5)
        - Pleadings, Pre-Trial Conferences--Memorandum on Radio Detector, 1961 (Box 238, Folder 6)
      - Dana Raymond Trial Book, undated (Box 238, Folder 7)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits--Diagrams, 1933-1941 (Box 238, Folder 8)
      - Letters, 1960 January 1-December 31 (Box 238, Folder 9)
      - Transcript of Proceedings, 1961 (Box 238)
      - Armstrong, E.H.--Mobile and Miscellaneous License Agreements, 1940-1949 (Box 238)
      - Memoranda of Law, 1957-1960, (3 Folders) (Box 238, Folder 10-12)
      - District Courts' Findings, Conclusions and Memoranda, 1964 (Box 238, Folder 13)
      - Briefs and Petitions for Rehearing, 1967 (Box 238, Folder 14)
      - Brief on Appeal and Appendix of Plaintiff-Appellee, Answer to Petition for Rehearing, undated (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - United States Court of Appeals for the Seventh District--Appendix for Brief for Defendant-Appellant--Volumes V and VI, 1966 (Box 239)
      - United States Court of Appeals for the Seventh District--Appendix for Brief for Defendant-Appellant--Volumes II-IV, 1966 (Box 245)
      - Suit for Infringement of Patents Binder, 1964, (3 Folders) (Box 239, Folder 2-4)
      - Demonstration of Similarity Between Horton Patent and Motorola Receivers--W.L. Everitt Presentation, 1961 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Order, undated (Box 239, Folder 6)
      - Suit Binder, 1964-1968 (Box 239)
      - Settlement Papers, 1968-1970 (Box 239, Folder 7)
      - Impartial Expert Testimony--Study on Proofs by Professor Palfrey et. al., 1958 (Box 239, Folder 8)
      - Drafts and Extra Copies, 1963, (3 Folders) (Box 239, Folder 9-11)
      - Heising Comments and Diagrams, 1960-1961 (Box 239, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1956-1957, (2 Folders) (Box 240, Folder 1-2)
      - Plaintiff's Memoranda and Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Heising Comments and Diagrams, 1960-1961 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Settlement Negotiations, 1957-1964, (2 Folders) (Box 240, Folder 5-6)
      - Motorola Service Manuals, 1958-1959 (Box 240, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda Regarding Proposed Stipulation, undated (Box 240, Folder 8)
      - Diagrams, undated (Box 240, Folder 9)
    - Armstrong vs. RCA
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1941-1951 (Box 240, Folder 10)
      - Notes on Breach of Contract and Royalty, undated (Box 240, Folder 11)
      - Excerpts of Transcript, undated (Box 240, Folder 12)
      - Summaries of Important Facts in Depositions of Witnesses, undated (Box 240, Folder 13)
      - Darby and Darby Report on Armstrong's FM Patents, 1950 (Box 240, Folder 14)
      - Patent Documents, 1937-1942 (Box 240, Folder 15)
      - Plaintiff's Memoranda, 1948 (Box 240, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence File, 1950-1956, (4 Folders) (Box 240, Folder 17-20)
      - Analysis of Circuit Diagrams Produced by RCA--D. Raymond, 1949 (Box 240)
      - Correspondence--D. Raymond, 1953 January 1-1954 February 4 (Box 240)
      - Byerly Notes--A. McCormack, 1949 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Notes by Byerly, 1940-1951 (Box 241, Folder 2)
      - Defendant's Memorandum Regarding Opposing Production Letter of November 10, 1939 from Schairer to Sarnoff, 1952 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Analysis of Hoxie's Examination, undated (Box 241, Folder 4)
      - Settlement, 1954 (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - Complaint and Composite, undated (Box 241, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda, 1952 (Box 241, Folder 7)
      - Exhibits, 1955 (Box 241, Folder 8)
      - Excerpts from McDonald Testimony, undated (Box 241, Folder 9)
      - Byerly's Papers, 1953-1954 (Box 241, Folder 10)
      - General Release and Covenants Not to Sue, 1954 (Box 241, Folder 11)
      - D.M. Raymond's Binder--General, 1948-1953, (3 Folders) (Box 241, Folder 12-14)
      - Legal Binder, 1954, (4 Folders) (Box 241, Folder 15-18)
    - Automatic Radio Manufacturing Co. Against Hazeltine Research, 1949 (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Columbia Alumni News Article--Draft, 1954 September 19 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Armstrong Portrait--Photograph, 1959 (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - "Thank You" Note Dictated by Marion Armstrong, 1959 (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - "Until I'm Dead or Broke"--Book Chapter, undated (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - "High Fidelity"--Draft of Play by Robert Mondlock, 1984 (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Litigation--General
      - Correspondence for Dana Raymond, 1944 (Box 242, Folder 7)
      - War Department Radio Manuals, 1945-1954, (4 Folders) (Box 242, Folder 8-11)
      - General, 1967-1969 (Box 242, Folder 12)
      - Contents of Files and D. M. Raymond's Bookcase, undated (Box 242, Folder 13)
      - "The Spirit of Discovery"--A.I.E.E., 1953 (Box 242, Folder 14)
      - Armstrong's Writings from Tom Styles, 1917-1961 (Box 242, Folder 15)
      - Crosby vs. Armstrong--Record for Armstrong, undated (Box 242, Folder 16)
      - De Forest Notes, 1912 June-1914 February (Box 242, Folder 17)
      - Patent Policies of RCA, 1939 (Box 242, Folder 18)
      - Radio Detector, All Cases--Exhibits and Patents, 1953-1959, (3 Folders) (Box 242, Folder 19-21)
      - RCA--Philco's Report on the RCA Radio Detector as Filed with the SEC, 1945 (Box 242, Folder 22)
      - RCA--Radio Detector--Publications and Instruction Manuals, undated (Box 242, Folder 23)
      - Radio Detector--All Cases, 1948-1950 (Box 242, Folder 24)
      - Publications, 1929-1982, (2 Folders) (Box 242, Folder 25-26)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibits
        - FM Publications, 1937-1948 (Box 242, Folder 27)
        - Correspondence Between Armstrong and Noble, 1936-1940 (Box 242, Folder 28)
      - FCC "Aural Broadcasting on Frequencies above 25,000 KC," 1940 March 19 (Box 242, Folder 29)
      - Mobile Communications, 1940 (Box 242, Folder 30)
      - Letter to D. Raymond, 1961 October 27 (Box 242, Folder 31)
      - Diagram of the Basic "Foster-Seeley" Discriminator, undated (Box 242, Folder 32)
      - Crosby Exhibit No. 51--Letter on Crosby Docket No. 6136 1932 March 24 (Box 242, Folder 33)
      - Letter to Lawrence Lessing from Town Biography, 1962 January 16 (Box 242, Folder 34)
      - General Electric Correspondence, 1940 (Box 242, Folder 35)
      - Unidentified Notes, undated (Box 242, Folder 36)
      - Broadcast Receiving Set License Agreements--A through Z, 1939-1952, (4 Folders) (Box 243, Folder 1-4)
      - "Sound Film AM-FM Comparisons Binder"
        - Descriptions of Reels, Transcripts and Notes, 1957 (Box 243, Folder 5)
        - Study of AM-FM Comparison Recordings Made for Armstrong by RCA Photophone, undated (Box 243, Folder 6)
      - "The Wideband FM Invention" by John Bose, 1936 (Box 243, Folder 7)
      - Proceedings of the IRE: Fiftieth Anniversary: 1912-1962 volume 50, Number 5, 1962 (Box 243)
      - Armstrong Agreements--Licenses
        - Receiver Agreements
          - General Electric, 1938-1945 (Box 243, Folder 8)
          - Garod Radio Corp., 1942 (Box 243, Folder 9)
          - Freed Radio Corp., 1940-1945 (Box 243, Folder 10)
          - Browning Laboratories, Inc., 1946 (Box 243, Folder 11)
          - Fisher Radio Corp., 1947-1952 (Box 243, Folder 12)
          - Fada Radio and Electric Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 243, Folder 13)
          - Espey Manufacturing Co, 1940 (Box 243, Folder 14)
          - Collins Audio Products, 1947 (Box 243, Folder 15)
          - Airadio, Inc., 1945 (Box 243, Folder 16)
          - Ansley Radio Corp., 1940-1941 (Box 243, Folder 17)
          - Meissner and Maguire, 1941-1945 (Box 243, Folder 18)
          - Minerva Corp. of America, 1945 (Box 243, Folder 19)
          - Magnavox Co., Inc., 1941 (Box 243, Folder 20)
          - Howard Radio Co., 1945 (Box 243, Folder 21)
          - Hammarlund, 1939 (Box 243, Folder 22)
          - Hallicrafters, Co., 1941 (Box 243, Folder 23)
      - Interoffice Memoranda, 1956 (Box 243, Folder 24)
      - Materials Regarding Motion to Substitute Plaintiff, 1955 (Box 243, Folder 25)
      - Royalties--General, 1946-1955 (Box 243, Folder 26)
      - Infringement Suits Other Than RCA, 1955-1965 (Box 243, Folder 27)
      - Broadcast Transmittal License Agreements, 1940-1946, (2 Folders) (Box 243, Folder 28-29)
      - Broadcast Transmittal License Agreements, 1946-1950, (4 Folders) (Box 244, Folder 1-4)
      - Information on Files Sent to Armstrong Memorial Research Foundation--Includes Litigation Documents, undated (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda Regarding Demonstrations, 1960 (Box 244, Folder 6)
      - "Antitrust Aspects of Effective Use of Patents…"--Address by Lionel Kestenbaum, 1967 March 2 (Box 244, Folder 7)
      - "E.H. Armstrong Estate: Patent and Licensing in Germany," 1954 August 9 (Box 244, Folder 8)
      - "The Man Behind Stereo FM"--Article in HiFi/Stereo Review, volume 7, No. 6, 1961 December (Box 244, Folder 9)
      - Court Decisions for Devex Corp. vs. GM and Devex vs. Houdaille Industries, 1959 (Box 244, Folder 10)
      - Radiant Burners vs. American Gas Association, People's Gas Light and Coke Co. et. al.--Appeal, 1963 (Box 244, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence Regarding John Marshall Law School Seminar Section on "The Armstrong FM Case," 1963 (Box 244, Folder 12)
      - Armstrong Patent Summaries, undated (Box 244, Folder 13)
      - "The History of Frequency Modulation," FM Radio-Electronics Engineering, undated (Box 244, Folder 14)
      - Armstrong v. RCA--"RCA Frequency Modulation"--Booklet Issued by Transmitter Advanced Development Section, 1939 December (Box 244, Folder 15)
      - De Forest Notes, 1912 June-1914 February (Box 244, Folder 16)
      - Patent, Royalty, and License Articles, 1946 (Box 244, Folder 17)
      - Armstrong Awards Address and Columbia University Engineering Dean's Day--Brochures, 1965-1966 (Box 244, Folder 18)
      - "The Super-Heterodyne-Its Origin, Development, and Some Recent Improvements" by Armstrong, 1919 (Box 244, Folder 19)
      - George Washington Pierce v. Aeronautical Communications Equipment--Brief, undated (Box 244, Folder 20)
      - "An Inventors' Vindication," Newsweek, 1967 October 30 (Box 244, Folder 21)
      - Armstrong Scripts--Correspondence, 1982 (Box 244, Folder 22)
      - Chronological History of Armstrong's Work--Negatives, undated (Box 244, Folder 23)
      - "The Proof of Scientific and Technical Facts in the Courts: Impartial Expert Testimony"--by John Gorham Palfrey, Professor of Law, Columbia University and Director of Research, Armstrong Project, 1957 June (volume) (Box 244)
      - Armstrong--D. Raymond's Memoranda, 1939-1940 (volume) (Box 244)
      - Trial Book Forms--Ed Carr of Cravath, Swaine and Moore, 1945 December 1 (2 copies) (volume) (Box 244)
      - "Method of Decreasing the Width of Channel Required for the Transmission of Speech or Other Forms of Intelligence" by Armstrong, 1930 April 16 (Box 244, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence with Armstrong Memorial Research Foundation Regarding Zenith, 1960--Excerpts from Depositions of E.McDonald, RCA vs. the Ravland Corp. and Zenith, 1956 (Box 244, Folder 25)
      - "Regeneration: Armstrong's First Invention" by Raymond Heising with Armstrong Memorial Research Foundation--Correspondence, Drafts and Charts, 1961-1962, (2 Folders) (Box 244, Folder 26-27)
    - Armstrong, Marion--Estate
      - Marion Armstrong--Personal Trust--Correspondence, 1963-1979, (2 Folders) (Box 245, Folder 1-2)
        - Account Documents, 1969-1982, (2 Folders) (Box 245, Folder 3-4)
    - Litigation
      - Unifilm Corp.--General Patent Matters, 1974-1982 (Box 245, Folder 5)
      - Reliability Research, Inc.
        - General, 1978 (Box 245, Folder 6)
        - Notes, undated (Box 245, Folder 7)
        - License Agreement A Form, undated (Box 245, Folder 8)
        - Investigation of License Agreements--Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 245, Folder 9)
        - Revision of the Book "You and the Law," 1977 (Box 245, Folder 10)
      - Armstrong vs. Emerson Radio and Phonograph Corp.
        - Drafts and Extra Copies of Settlement Agreements and Papers Terminating Suit, 1960 (Box 245, Folder 11)
      - License Agreements, 1939-1957, (2 Folders) (Box 245, Folder 12-13)
      - Plaintiff's Exhibit-- FM Magazine, 1940 November, 1941 April (Box 245)
      - Microfilm--35mm (Box 246)
        - Unidentified Armstrong Litigation--1958-1961 (5 rolls) (Box 246)
  - Pennie and Edmonds--Volumes (Box 209)
    - United State District Court Southern District of New York, United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Record and Opinion, 1921 (Box 209)
    - United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Briefs and Opinions, 1922 (Box 209)
    - United State District Court Southern District of New York, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Briefs and Opinions, 1921 (Box 209)
    - United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Transcript of Record, 1921 (Box 209)
    - United State District Court Southern District of New York, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Briefs in Regard to De Forest D 17 Receiver, 1925 (Box 209)
    - United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Briefs, 1922 (Box 209)
    - United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Preliminary Injunction Regarding D-17, Transcript of Record, Briefs, 1925 (Box 210)
    - United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Record, De Forest Contempt, Proceedings, 1923 (Box 210)
    - United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit, E.H. Armstrong and Westinghouse Electric and Manufacturing Co. vs. Irving Langmuir and General Electric Co. and Lee De Forest; De Forest Radio Telephone and Telegraph Co; Alexander Meissner; Secretary of the Navy; American Telephone and Telegraph Co.--Transcript of Record, Briefs, Under Rev. Sec. 4915, 1924-1926 (Box 210)
    - Court of Appeals of the District of Columbia, E.H. Armstrong vs. Lucien Levy, Interference No. 52,088--Briefs and Record, 1927 (Box 210)
    - United States Patent Office and Court of Appeals--Interference Volume I, Armstrong vs. De Forest vs. Langmuir vs. Meissner--Transcript of Record Volume I, 1921 (Box 210)
    - United States Patent Office and Court of Appeals--Interference Volume II, Armstrong vs. De Forest vs. Langmuir vs. Meissner--Transcript of Record Volume II, 1923 (Box 211)
    - United States Patent Office and Court of Appeals--Interference Volume III, Armstrong vs. De Forest vs. Langmuir vs. Meissner--Briefs Before Examiner and Board, 1921-1922 (Box 211)
    - United States Patent Office and Court of Appeals--Interference Volume IV, Armstrong vs. De Forest vs. Langmuir vs. Meissner--Briefs Before Commissioner and Court of Appeals, 1922-1923 (Box 211)
- Series VI: Photographs, Negatives and Lantern Slides, 1886-1967
  This series contains photographic media, arranged alphabetically. They are separated into two different types of materials; photographs with the negatives, followed by lantern slides. The series spans the course of Armstrong's life including childhood, military service in WWI, and his work in the Marcellus Hartley Laboratory at Columbia University. Images of the apparatus used in the development of regenerative circuit, the superheterodyne circuit and FM radio are also included. The FM-radio materials include the first tests of FM at the Empire State Building, Westhampton Beach, New York and Haddonfield, New Jersey, construction and operation of the first FM tower at Alpine, NJ, and the Yankee Network. Lantern slides that are duplicated in the photographs or negative are marked as "duplicate."
  - General
    - Apparatus
      - 2660 Megacycle Receiver and Transmitter On Test Bench In Electronic Laboratory Car With Automatic Recording Instruments, undated (Box 265, Folder 1)
      - Apparatus In Tent at Ardrossan, Scotland, undated (Box 265, Folder 2)
      - De Forest Audion Detector; Receiving Cabinet, undated (Box 265, Folder 3)
      - Description of Lantern Slides, undated (Box 265, Folder 4)
      - Empire State Building; FM Transmitters Installed By Armstrong, E.H., 1934-1935 (Box 265, Folder 5)
      - FM Radio--Apparatus Used in the First Presentation of FM to the Engineering World, Reception of W2AG Broadcast from Yonkers, NY, 1935 November (Box 265, Folder 6)
      - General Electric FM Radio Set, undated (Box 265, Folder 7)
      - Installation of the "Runyon Transmitter" On the Chimney of Randy Runyon's Beach House in Mantoloking, New Jersey, undated (includes negative) (Box 265, Folder 8)
      - Original Components of the Regenerative Circuit, undated (Box 265, Folder 9)
      - S.S. President Harding Experimental Facsimile Receiver for Daily Reception of Complete Weather Maps, undated (Box 265, Folder 10)
      - Turbines and Generators--Chicago Edison, Boston Edison, Commonwealth Edison, [1915] (Box 265, Folder 11)
      - U.H.Apparatus [Labeled “Criswell Photos”], 1934-1936, 1939-1941 (Box 265, Folder 12)
      - Washington Apparatus-- Includes Correspondence from Weigant to Hughes, 1926 March 19 (Box 265, Folder 13)
      - Unidentified Apparatus, 1920, 1936-1937 (Box 265, Folder 14)
      - Unidentified Apparatus, undated (includes negatives) (Box 265, Folder 15)
      - Unidentified Apparatus [Possibly Power Amplifier], undated (Box 265, Folder 16)
    - Armstrong, E.H.
      - Armstrong, E.H., 1940 May 8 (Box 265, Folder 17)
      - Armstrong, E.H. and Paul De Mars at Westhampton Beach, 1947 (Box 265, Folder 18)
      - Armstrong, E.H. and Unidentified in Academic Robes; Wilson-Degree at Columbia University, undated (Box 265, Folder 19)
      - Armstrong, E.H. Holding a Trophy Next to Unidentified Holding a Tennis Racket, Vermont, undated (Box 265, Folder 20)
      - Armstrong, E.H. In Later Life, Portrait by Fabian Bachrach, undated (Box 265, Folder 21)